<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Gabriele Abbate</title>
    <link>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Gabriele Abbate</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 23:45:37 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Paprikà - Time Tracking Device</title>
      <link>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/paprika/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Sep 2023 23:45:37 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/paprika/</guid>
      <description>Mar 2023 - Jun 2023&#xA;For an innovation and entrepreneurship university course, my team and I embarked on a journey to conceptualize, design, and develop a revolutionary product known as Paprikà. This innovative device, shaped like a paprika, seamlessly blends the realms of technology, business acumen, and practicality. Our project&amp;rsquo;s focus was divided equally between innovation and business aspects, and the technical competencies required to bring our idea to life, from 3D printing the device to creating a robust platform with integrated APIs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Adversarial Examples Evading Deepfake-Image Detectors with White-Box Attacks</title>
      <link>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/adversarial/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 19:01:48 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/adversarial/</guid>
      <description>Jan 2023 - Aug 2023&#xA;The project involved conducting in-depth research based on Carlini and Farid&amp;rsquo;s paper into potential white and black box attacks on ResNet50, aiming to significantly reduce the classifier&amp;rsquo;s accuracy to near 0%. Subsequently, one of the proposed white-box attacks (a Loss-Maximizing-like attack) was implemented to attack the ResNet50 model fine-tuned with the TrueFace dataset provided by the University of Trento.&#xA;The ultimate goal of the project was to enable ResNet50 to misclassify all the fake images extracted from the database and to make it falsely identify these images as real.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Enhancing Thera Mental Health App: Integrating Ai-Powered Safety Measures for Improved User Well-Being</title>
      <link>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/thera/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Sep 2023 18:59:55 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/thera/</guid>
      <description>Jul 2023 - Aug 2023&#xA;The project was developed by my team, made of five students from different European universities, during our Summer School organized by EIT Digital Master School.&#xA;Our team played a pivotal role in advancing Thera (a Lithuanian mental health app) by integrating AI-driven safety measures. By implementing a carefully designed decision-tree logic and dynamic AI filtering, we ensured that user interactions with the app were guided towards safer outcomes.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Robust Image Watermarking</title>
      <link>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/image_watermarking/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Oct 2022 00:03:57 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/image_watermarking/</guid>
      <description>Oct 2022 - Dec 2022&#xA;The Robust Image Watermarking is a technique based on Discrete Wavelet Transform (DWT) and All Phase Discrete Cosine Biorthogonal Transform (APDCBT), implemented for the &amp;ldquo;Multimedia Data Security&amp;rdquo; project.&#xA;To read the paper on which this implementation was based, go here.&#xA;Since this project was destined for a final exam, in which we had to implement the most resilient watermarking technique while attacking the others, I also worked on a couple of scripts that implement attacks used with the end goal of ruining the other teams&amp;rsquo; watermarks without compromising the Weighted Peak Signal-to-Noise Ratio (WPSNR).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A Robust Fingerprint Data Encryption Technique for High Security Applications</title>
      <link>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 17 Sep 2022 18:57:26 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/thesis/</guid>
      <description>Feb 2022 - Jul 2022&#xA;Project about biometric encryption for my bachelor thesis. I have developed an efficient algorithm for fingerprint recognition and matching. This algorithm served as the foundation of my research, which entails the implementation of a fast and highly secure algorithm of encryption and decryption using Shamir&amp;rsquo;s Secret Sharing scheme.&#xA;Image Processing The first part of the algorithm provides a sequence of operations aimed at making the input image as clear and legible as possible, in order to facilitate the minutiae extraction process.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Epidemiological Simulator</title>
      <link>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/epidemiological_simulator/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2020 21:39:15 +0100</pubDate>
      <guid>https://morebaconstrips.github.io/projects/epidemiological_simulator/</guid>
      <description>Mar 2020 - Jun 2020&#xA;The “Epidemiological Simulator” is a Java program designed to simulate the spread of infectious diseases within different populations. This interactive and educational tool allows users to explore various scenarios and strategies for managing epidemics. Whether you’re interested in modeling the dynamics of a well-known virus like COVID-19 or creating custom scenarios with different parameters, this program offers a flexible platform for experimentation.&#xA;Key Features: Educational Tool: This program serves has been an educational tool for understanding and applying in real world scenarios OOP concepts, such as inheritance, polymorphism, encapsulation, and abstraction.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
